(Sheldon:)Mom, I want to apologize
for my behavior last night.
(Mrs Cooper:)Apology accepted.
Great. Now, you're gonna love
the Perlmutter lecture.
(Sheldon:)Look, he will be stating that the universe
is older than 6000 years...
...but you could stick
your fingers in your ears...
...and hum "Amazing Grace"
during those parts.
(Mrs Cooper:)I am still going out with your friends.
(Sheldon:)But I apologized.
(Sheldon:)And that was hard for me
because I didn't do anything wrong.
(Mrs Cooper:)Shelly, I hung out with you
in enough dusty lecture halls...
(Mrs Cooper:)...while you were growing up.
I wanna go sightseeing.
(Mrs Cooper:)So why don't you have some pancakes,
get dressed and come with us.
(Sheldon:)I'm not going, and you can't make me.
(Mrs Cooper:)You're right, I can't. Have a nice day.
(Sheldon:)Well, I'm going to stand here
until you change your mind.
Then you are gonna stand there
all day.
(Leonard:)I'm just gonna take my bacon grease
and slide over there.
(Sheldon:)I can't believe my own mother
is abandoning me.